heybingo.com 2016-05-16

# Free Bingo Games Online at HeyBingo.com

HeyBingo is committed to you and to protecting your privacy. The information we collect about you is used to provide you with a more personalized and richer experience while visiting our site.

Please note that when you link to other sites from HeyBingo, the Online Privacy Policy cannot control the activities on those other sites and our policy therefore does not apply to these other sites. We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time, so it is important for you to check back periodically to ensure that you are aware of our policies that are in force at any given time.

## HOW DOES HEYBINGO COLLECT INFORMATION?

**IP Address**  
When a user visits HeyBingo, we may collect the IP (internet protocol) address that requested the display of our website. We use the IP address to promote our ability to restrict access to the site by users who abuse our Terms of Service agreement. It may also be used to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website tracking to gather broad, demographic information.

**Cookies**  
HeyBingo uses a feature on your Internet web browser called a "cookie". A cookie is a small piece of information stored on your hard drive. It helps us maintain your preferences between visits to provide a personalized experience for you. Data stored in a cookie by HeyBingo is only accessible by the HeyBingo website.

HeyBingo uses cookies to tell us whether or not you have visited our website before, as well as storing your sign-in details so that we may automatically log you in each time you visit HeyBingo from that same computer. We also collect non-personally identifiable information, such as anonymous session numbers, with them.

## WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

HeyBingo does not house or collect any personal information about you unless you knowingly and willingly provide it.

**Membership Registration**  
HeyBingo has a registration process through which you voluntarily sign up in order to play our games and access members-only site features. During the registration process, we ask for your email address. Also to make sure that nobody else can access your account using your name or identity, we ask that you create a unique screen name with a password.

**Player Profile**  
In your Profile page, you may also specify OPTIONAL information like your birth date and your gender. Except for your chosen screen name, everything else remain private. As we add more features to the site, you may optionally show other information when other players view your profile. What other players see will be in your full control.

**Newsletter Subscription**  
When you sign up as a HeyBingo user, by default the option will be selected to allow us to communicate with you via email about games, news, special offers and events. You have the option to "uncheck" the box on the sign-up form that corresponds with this, although by doing so you are potentially asking us not to notify you of important events or site announcements. Any email that we send to you will also have instructions at the the bottom that will allow you to opt out of any further mailings. Also, you will always be able to return to your player Profile page and reset this option if your preference changes at a later date.

**Contests and Promotions**  
HeyBingo does NOT guarantee regular contests, but from time to time, we may hold such events. When you enter a contest or take part in a promotion, we may ask for your name, mailing address, email address or any other information pertinent to the specific promotion. Should a third party sponsor the contest or promotion, that party will have access to this information. We need this information in order to notify our winners and, when applicable, ship the winners' prizes.

## DOES HEYBINGO EVER SHARE INFORMATION WITH OTHER PARTIES?

**Disclosure of Information to Outside Parties**  
HeyBingo collects demographic and profile data, which is aggregated and may be shared with third-party sites. Your personal information (e.g. e-mail address) is never shared or sold to any third-party site. The only time your personal information may be shared is if you join and win any contest or promotion as discussed in the previous paragraph. Under some limited and special circumstances, we may also disclose this information if there is a violation of our Terms of Service Agreement or if we have a good faith belief that the law requires it.

**Links to Outside Third Parties**  
HeyBingo may establish relationships with reputable business partners by creating a link between our sites. HeyBingo chooses its business partners carefully. We are not, however, responsible for the content, maintenance or privacy policies of those sites. Once you click over to a third-party site, we encourage you to check their privacy policy.

Users who click over to a third-party site from a link on HeyBingo must be aware that HeyBingo makes no warranties with regard to that site's policies or business practices. HeyBingo is not responsible for any transactions that occur between the user and the third-party site. Should a user purchase any products or services from that third-party site, the user must contact the third-party site directly regarding any disputes that might occur, including, but not limited to: delayed shipping, missing products, damaged goods, or pricing or billing discrepancies. HeyBingo is not responsible for the actions of any third-party site.

**Chat and Messaging Facilities**  
HeyBingo may have chat rooms and/or message boards, where users can exchange ideas and communicate with one another. When posting to a message board or chat area, it is important for you to understand that the information is being made publicly available in an on-line environment. Posting such information is the sole responsibility of the individual user. Exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. As these forums are public and open for users to interact with each other, HeyBingo expects all its users to respect the rights of others.

## AGREEMENT IN PRINCIPLE WITH HEYBINGO POLICIES

By using HeyBingo, you signify your understanding of and assent to the Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, we strongly urge that you do not use the HeyBingo website.
